trueknowledge.com 2016-05-13

# Evi - Privacy Policy

Evi Technologies Limited is committed to protecting the privacy and confidentiality of information provided by all users of Evi, evi.com and its other products.

Please read the following privacy policy to understand how we use and protect the information that is provided to us by users of our products.

By using our products, visiting and/or registering on this site, you consent to the collection, use and transfer of your information under the terms of this policy.

### Information that we collect from you via the Evi software and service

When you download and use Evi you may be asked to provide certain information about yourself to provide you with a better experience with Evi.

Evi will optionally ask for your name. This will be stored securely on our servers and is used to provide a more personalised experience with Evi.

Evi will optionally request permission to connect to partner services of which you may have an account with.

This is to allow Evi to learn more about you to provide you with a better, more personalised experience. Any data stored is subject to the partner's terms of service and is solely for the use of Evi - it will not be shared with any other third party.

When you use the Evi Software and Service, location data from your mobile device is transmitted to and stored on our servers to provide relevant local information. Text input and speech data, including transcripts of speech utterances via the Evi Software are may also be stored to enable the Service to provide the relevant information for your needs and to improve future responses. Certain device information may also be transmitted to and stored on our servers that may uniquely identify your device. This includes: 

  * IP address
  * Make and model of device
  * Operating system version

We also use, within the Evi mobile application, Flurry Services in order to collect statistical data about your usage of our application, without infringing your privacy rights. This data is used to improve the services offered to you. Flurry is not responsible for any use by us of any data about you.

If you do not want Flurry to track data from your device you can opt-out by clicking on this link: <http://www.flurry.com/resources/privacy.html>

Speech recognition is provided by Nuance Communications or may be provided by other parties who may use speech data created by you to improve the performance of their service and to train, tune, enhance and improve the speech recognition and other components of its software and services. If you wish to learn more, please visit <http://www.nuance.com/company/company-overview/company-policies/privacy-policies/index.htm>

### Information that we collect from you

When you visit or register on <https://www.evi.com/> (and all other subdomains of evi.com) you may be asked to provide certain information about yourself including your name, contact details and credit or debit card information. We may also collect information about your use of our website as well as information about you by the use of cookies (see below), information you post to the website and e-mails or letters you send to us.

### Information that we collect from you via the Evi Technologies browser add-on

When you use the Evi Technologies browser add-on (also called Google Enhancer - True Knowledge and the True Knowledge Firefox add-on), the add-on will transmit to Evi Technologies servers information relating to your use of certain internet search engines. This information includes the search terms you use, what search engine you are using and which version of the add-on you have installed. All use of the add-on is anonymous, we do not associate any personally identifiable information with the information transmitted to our servers via the add-on.

### Information posted by third parties

Users of this website may submit personal information about third parties to the Evi Technologies database through this website. We do not verify the content of any personal information posted to this website by third parties over whom we have no control. Although every reasonable effort is made to ensure that the information on this website is accurate at the time of publication, it is subject to variation at any time without notice and Evi Technologies gives no warranty whatsoever that any such information will be accurate or complete at any particular time. Please refer to our [terms of use](https://www.evi.com/legal/ "terms of use") for further information. We reserve the right at any time and at our sole discretion to remove any information or to correct any information which has been posted to this website.

### Cookies

Cookies are small amounts of information which are stored on your computer. Using cookies enables us to monitor website traffic and to personalise the content of our site to your requirements. This maximises the benefits you gain in using our website and makes it easier for you to log on and use the site during any future visits.

We may use cookies to collect information about your use of our website (whether you register on our site or not). As soon as you enter or register on our site, our system will issue cookies to your computer whenever you log on.

The first time you use the Evi Technologies browser add-on, our service sends a cookie to your computer. The cookie is used to facilitate the collection of the information described in the paragraph above titled: Information that we collect from you when you use the Evi Technologies browser add-on.

You may disable the use of cookies in your internet browser but this may limit your access to our website or adversely affect your use of features or functions on certain web pages on it.

### Use of your information

The information we collect from you will enable us to provide you with access to all parts of our website and the services you have requested. We will also keep records of those who have requested access to secure parts of our website and use and analyse the information we collect so that we can administer, support, improve and develop our business.

In particular, we may use the information we collect from you to contact you for your views on our products and services and to notify you occasionally about important changes or developments to them or to the site. Where you have consented to us doing so, we might also use the information we collect from you to let you know about other products and services which we offer which may be of interest to you and we may contact you by post, telephone or fax, as well as by e-mail. If you change your mind about being contacted in the future, please let us know.

### Information that we collect from you via the Evi software and service

When you download and use Evi you may be asked to provide certain information about yourself to provide you with a better experience with Evi.

Evi will optionally ask for your name. This will be stored securely on our servers and is used to provide a more personalised experience with Evi.

Evi will optionally request permission to connect to partner services of which you may have an account with. This is to allow Evi to learn more about you to provide you with a better, more personalised experience. Any data stored is subject to the partner's terms of service and is solely for the use of Evi - it will not be shared with any other third party.

When you use the Evi Software and Service, location data from your mobile device may be transmitted to and stored on our servers to provide relevant local information. Text input and speech data, including transcripts of speech utterances via the Evi Software are also stored to enable the Service to provide the relevant information for your needs and to improve future responses. Certain device information may also be transmitted to and stored on our servers that may uniquely identify your device.

### Disclosure of your information

When you post knowledge and/or other materials to this website, you will be identified as having posted such information by whatever user name you selected when you registered with this website.

evi.com is a community powered question answering site where the community can help get questions answered by adding and correcting knowledge. For this reason, questions that you ask on the www.evi.com website may be published for the benefit of other users.

To avoid personal identification, we will not without your express consent, associate your user name or other identifiable information with the questions asked, nor will we group your questions together as being associated with a single user.

The information you provide to us will be held on our computers in the EEA and may be accessed by or transferred to companies within the Evi Technologies group and third parties located outside of the EEA, some of whom are located in the US who provide services for us and for the purposes set out in this policy. Those third parties process information, process credit card payments and provide support services on our behalf. We may also pass aggregate information on the usage of our site to third parties but this will not include information that can be used to identify you. Whenever we transfer information to countries outside of the EEA as described above, we will ensure that the information is transferred in accordance with this Privacy policy and applicable data protection laws.

Finally, if we enter into a joint venture or our business is sold to or merged with another business entity, your information may be disclosed to our new business partners or owners. Countries outside the European Economic Area do not always have strong data protection laws. However, we will always take steps to ensure that your information is used by third parties in accordance with this policy and applicable data protection laws.

Unless required to do so by law or as otherwise set out in this privacy policy, we will not share, sell or distribute any of your personal information without your consent.

We only collect information via the Evi Technologies Firefox add-on in order to facilitate the function of the add-on and for internal statistical and analytical use. The information we collect via the add-on is kept private.

### Protection of personal data

We employ security measures to protect your information from access by unauthorised persons and against unlawful processing, accidental loss, destruction and damage. We will retain your information for a reasonable period or as long as the law requires.

### Links

Evi Technologies is not responsible for the privacy and data protection practices of other websites which may be reached through links contained in this website. Users should be aware when they leave this website and move into any linked website and should read the privacy and data protection policies and statements contained on any such linked website.

### Accessing and updating

You are entitled to see the information held about you and you may ask us to make any necessary changes to ensure that it is accurate and kept up to date. If you wish to do this, please contact us. We are entitled by law to charge a fee of Â£10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

### Changes to our privacy policy

Any changes to our privacy policy in the future will be posted to the site and, where appropriate, through e-mail notification.

### Contact

All comments, queries and requests relating to our use of your information are welcomed and should be addressed to William Tunstall-Pedoe at Evi Technologies Limited, Poseidon House, Castle Park, Cambridge, United Kingdom, CB3 0RD, United Kingdom or at [privacy@evi.com](mailto:privacy@evi.com) .
